# Samyra Cury Salek

Brighton, UK

samyracsalek@gmail.com Phone: +44 07305 759339 Post Code: BN1 3TP

### **Summary**

I am a self-motivated master graduate with 7 years of professional and volunteer experience seeking a customer facing position in a company that wishes to create and improve processes. I enjoy tackling challenges with strong communication, leadership and research skills, aiming to increase visibility and profit.

### Education

2015 - 2016

Karlshochschule International University, Karlsruhe, Germany, MA in Management.

2008 - 2012

ESB Business School, Reutlingen, Germany, International Business Course.

2008 - 2012

Georgetown University, Washington DC, USA, Communicative Skills Seminar.

2008 - 2012

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Campinas, Campinas, Brazil, BSc in Tourism.

### Experience

## **Basepoint Business Centre**

Sep 2018 - Present

Community Manager

- Active develop and maintain effective relationships with customers, teams and suppliers.
- Ensure the achievement of the centre financial goals and objectives.
- Develop, implementation and maintain all social media and marketing action.

#### Trend in Africa

Aug 2015 - Jul 2018

Project Manager

- Manage 170,000 euros donated by the Volkswagen Institute for this 3-year project;
- Courses and workshops organization in different African countries.
- Multitask role ranging from students' applications, design of course schedule to engaging with community relationship, lecturers and suppliers from different countries.
- Development and implementation of all courses activities ensuring positive local social impact.

## TUBEX Holding

Aug 2014 - Feb 2017

Account Manager

- Daily management of client's relationship and satisfaction.
- Responsible for projects reports, setting management client success targets between Brazil and Germany sites.
- Develop of internal and external documentation (score cards, CSR, CDP and Environmental Reports), increasing business opportunities with companies such as L'Oréal Paris, Natura &Co and Beiersdorf AG.

Assistant Marketing Manager

- Processing of prospective master students' applications.
- Construction and maintenance of student's profile and information databases.
- Management of social media presence (e.g. Facebook, LinkedIn) with advertisement and creation of newsfeed groups

### **Luna Consulting**

May 2014 - Oct 2014

 $Staff\ Specialist$ 

- Owner of full-cycle recruiting process for multiple global business clients.
- Sourcing & interviewing of technical roles candidates for clients.
- Management of online job posting and applicant tracking system.

### Meta Social Institute

Jan 2013 - Jul 2013

Project Manager

Development and delivery of a social projects for integration of adults with Down syndrome, focusing on basic independent skills.

#### IBM Brazil

Jan 2011 - May 2012

Assistant Project Manager

- Member of the team responsible for Delta Airlines business account.
- Support to project managers around the world, being the focal point for assigning all professionals to their projects.
- Mediator of meetings, responsible for weekly and monthly financial reports and projects progress worldwide.
- Assisting strategic projects decisions and implementations.

### Strengths

- Extend project management; quick to pick up new things and teach others
- Communicative, highly organised, honest, creative and collaborative with the team
- Strong computer skills, including MS Office
- Strong data and fact-based analysis
- Good written and verbal communication skills

Skills Base

Languages: Fluent in Portuguese and English. Proficient in Spanish and German;

More Info

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/samyra-salek-851a1265/